tauedu.org 2015-06-10

# Texila American University Privacy Policy | TAU Privacy Policy

#### Scope

This policy is applicable for the current and former students of TAU, visitors of the website, and any other user who uses the services offered by the Texila American University. These may include websites or any mobile applications operated by and on their behalf. This policy relates to offline and online collection, storage, and transfer of Personal Information.

Some of the sites or services may come under the control of additional privacy policies or disclosures. These services are called "Additional Policies". If there is any conflict between any Additional Policies and policy, the Additional Policies will control.

The Texila American University may alter these Privacy Policies at any time, so the visitors should periodically check these policies for any updates. Contents

  * Definitions
  * Information We Collect
  * Information Collected Automatically
  * Information You Provide to Us
  * How We Use This Information
  * Location of Information Processing
  * Online Behavioural Advertising
  * Opt Out
  * Our Security Measures
  * Call Monitoring
  * Internet Technologies Used
  * Site Hosting and Links From Our Sites to Other Websites
  * Privacy Policy Changes
  * How to Access Your Information and Contact Us
  * Safe senders list

The terms used in this privacy policy have the following definitions and meanings. They are as follows:

#### Definitions

"Business Associates" means they are the third party service providers to which the Texila American University may contract with them to provide services on our behalf. This include the Social Networking, hosting, web analytics, Online Behavioural Advertising, lead generation, academic, business, career, or financial services.

"Educational Partners" of Texila American University have their subsidiaries and other affiliates including educational institutions or agents providing educational related services under a contract. 

"Financial Information" indicates particular Personal Information of financial characteristics such as your credit card number. This collected information may include: Personal Information, Financial Information, Web Analytical Information or any other Details gathered from you through our Websites. "Personal Information" means Details that may be used, alone to recognize a particular people and contains financial information. 

“Online Behavioural Advertising” means the collection of data from a particular computer or device regarding web viewing behaviours for the purpose of using such data to predict user interests to deliver advertising to that computer from such Web viewing behaviours.

"Site" or "Sites", means websites operated by or on behalf of Texila American University, regardless of domain name or IP address.

"Social Network", means various communication technologies used in the internet that facilitate conversation and interaction between people in online and includes, blogs, discussion forums, wikis, chat sessions, news groups, etc.

"Social Network Content" or "SNC" means user-generated content you may share via a Social Network. It includes Personal Information, videos, and pictures that you may upload to a Social Network and visible to every user of a Social Network pages.

"Your University" means University of Phoenix.

"We", "us", and "our" refer to the group of Texila American University.

"Unrelated Entities" means third parties who are not provides educational services as Educational Partners and as Business Associates.

"Web Analytical Information" means internet generated Information we collect when you visit our Sites. Then This Information may be linked with the Personal Information and the university may contact you for identical purpose. All the details we collected are kept safe 

#### How We Collect Information

We collect various types of Information from you through our websites where you can express interest in our services, through mobile applications, over the phone, or printed forms, and in person. Some Information is collected automatically through various web technologies including Social Networking tools used by our University. 

Sometimes we get Information when you provide it to us voluntarily. We may also obtain information from Educational Partners and Unrelated Entities Information Collected Automatically on the Sites

Web Analytical Information automatically gathers all the information whenever you visit one of our sites. In general, the collected details do not recognize you personally. Examples of Web Analytical Information include, but are not limited to:

  * IP address
  * Collection Date
  * Publisher Name
  * Connection Speed
  * Day and time of the Week 
  * Language settings
  * Country, State, Designated Market Area (DMA), City 
  * Domain (.com, .net, .mil, .org, .edu, etc.)

This Information may be linked with Personal Information to get the specifications described in this privacy policy

#### Information You Provide to Us

In addition to the Web Analytical Information TAU also collects, uses, and discloses Personal Information that you provide to us voluntarily online or offline when you respond to an advertisement, a survey, or a request for information; register for classes; apply for financial aid; set up a Social Network or other Site profile; or use one of our career resources, learning assessments or other interactive tools. While the nature of the Personal Information may vary depending on the type of response or service requested, the following is a non-exclusive list of the types of Details that may be gathered it is necessary and appropriate for the required purposes:

  * First, Middle and Last Name, Previous Names
  * Street Address, City, State, Country, Postal Code
  * Date of Birth 
  * Place of Birth 
  * Gender 
  * Race 
  * Ethnicity 
  * Country of origin 
  * Employment History
  * Native Language 
  * Address Type 
  * E-mail address 
  * Valid Telephone Number 
  * Cell Phone Number 
  * Confirmation of the age of majority 
  * Campus 
  * TAU Institution interested in 
  * Current degree program of interest 
  * Current modality of interest (online, on-ground or Flexnet) 
  * Publisher Code (Site ID) 
  * Citizenship
  * No. of Previous Credits 
  * Military Affiliation 
  * Credits earned 
  * Prior Education History 
  * High School Diploma 
  * Lead Source 
  * Individual Record Number (IRN) or Social Security Number 
  * Credit Card Number 
  * Other Financial Information and information related to financial aid 
  * Social Networking Content
  * Learning, Skill, or Career Assessment data
  * Career Goals 
  * After you become a University student other information such as course assignments, grades and other educational records relating to your enrolment may be required to be collected in the normal course of your studies at our university.

#### How We Use and Disclose This Information

We will not sell or misuse your Personal Information to third party agents except in accordance with this policy.

We may collect, use, and disclose your personal Information for the following purposes:

  * to figure out your admissibility and to signup you for the best academic applications
  * to provide requested goods and services 
  * to reply to your queries and provide client support
  * to provide information in which you have indicated as a interest
  * for our internal marketing purposes, which includes, but is not limited to, sending you details about products, services, updates, etc. that we think may be of interest to you 
  * for fostering communication and collaboration among members of our University community through Social Networks
  * for discussing with our Academic Associates who may get in touch with you with regard to their educational or other services 
  * for sharing with our Educational Partners or Business Associates who are performing services on our behalf 
  * to evaluate how Websites and services are being accessed and used
  * for Online Behavioural Advertising purposes 
  * to enhance Site performance and delivery
  * to prevent potentially illegal activities (including downloading of copyrighted materials according to our Infringement policy) 
  * to analyze academic outcomes and preferences of studying
  * to analyze risk and business results
  * to acquire transaction for services that we provide to you 
  * to offer you with details concerning preparations and other choices for the repayment of resources financed to you for your education
  * to maintain business records 
  * to enforce our Terms of Use
  * to provide to Educational Partners, Business Associates or Unrelated Entities in connection with the actual reorganization, merger, acquisition, financing, securitization, insuring, sale or other disposal of our business, including purposes of determining whether to proceed with such transaction or fulfilling any records. In the event of any actual reorganization, such Information may be transferred as part of the transaction to the acquirer 

#### Financial Information

Your Financial Information will be used to provide requested services, to analyze operational and business results for concluding your registration or other transaction you have initiated with us. It will not be sold, rented, or transferred to an Educational Partner, Business Associate, or Unrelated Entity

#### Location of Information Processing

Our university processes information in multiple jurisdictions and some Educational Partners and Business Associates may use other laws of jurisdiction. In such cases, your Personal Information may be collected, used, stored and disclosed in these jurisdiction for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. The data protection and other laws might differ from your jurisdiction. We require our Educational Partners and Business Associates to use your Personal Information according to this plan and to take affordable steps to ensure that your comfort is secured according to appropriate laws. Your Details may be subject to the regulations of those other areas, including legal requirements to reveal Personal Details to nations.

#### Online Behavioural Advertising

Our online advertisements and Sites taking part in Online Behavioural Advertising that help consumers to understand how their data is being. Some of these ads are focused on your interests depending on your browsing history, which is saved in a cookie. Your browsing history may be monitored in these cookies even if ads are not being shown.

#### Opt-Out

**Marketing Communications**  
If you do not wish to receive marketing email communications from us, you may express your choice where indicated on the applicable email. If you do not wish to receive marketing telephone calls or mailings, you may express your choice to opt-out by emailing [info@tauedu.org](mailto:info@tauedu.org).

Marketing opt-out requests will only remove you from our list and the list of any Business Associate performing services on our behalf. We are not responsible for the use any other party may make of the Information once it has been transferred in accordance with this Policy and you will need to contact such entity to have your Information removed from their database.

Student Educational Records and Social Networking Content

Students who desire to prevent release of their directory and educational record Information in accordance with FERPA may place a FERPA Hold on their academic file. Click here to review your University's FERPA Policy.

You may change user settings related to sharing your Personal Information contained in any user profile as part of Social Network activities furnished by us. Note that your withdrawal from Social network might avoid us from offering you with certain goods and services. 

#### Our Security Measures

The TAU will provide reasonable security measures to store and secure your Information to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the Information under our control. We implement standard security measures when recognizing your bank card details during the online process, as well as whenever we ask youto sign in to any of our Websites.

Unfortunately, the data transmission over the web cannot be assured to be absolutely protected. Consequently, although we will implement such actions, we do not guarantee you against the loss, misuse, or difference in Details under our management, and let you at your own risk. You should always take care with how you manage and reveal your personal details and should prevent delivering personal details through vulnerable e-mail, Public Systems or other internet programs.

#### Monitoring of Communications

We may observe and maintain all inbound and confident communication for exercising of our associates and for quality requirements. Such communications are only maintained as long as necessary to release these requirements. If you want that your communications not be maintained for any purpose, please recommend your associate.

#### Internet Technologies Used

Cookies, web search, and other relevant technologies are used on our Sites to allow us to achieve the uses to provide sites messaging and to keep a record of your Information. This program saved in your web browser and can be eliminated. If you want to eliminate such technology you may do so, but this may provide our Sites unusable to you. You can opt out of cookies or other technology used to turn off these features in your web browser. Please observe that the removal of certain opt-out cookies may require you to restore your Online Behavioural Promotion opt-outs regularly. Visit your web browser's "Help" menu for assistance in changing cookies configurations or eliminating cookies data files.

#### Site Hosting and Links from Our Sites to Other Websites

Some of our Sites may contain links to websites hosted by Educational Partners, Unrelated Entities, and Business Associates operating websites on their own behalf or on behalf of multiple entities. Some of these websites may collect your Personal Information and may apply their own policies on how your Personal Information is used. In addition, some of our Sites may have Additional Policies that apply to the use of Personal Information collected on that Site. Please make sure to read the policies of any websites you visit on the internet carefully. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of any websites that are not operated by or exclusively for us, and the collection, use, and disclosure of Information about you will be subject to the policies applicable on those websites.

#### Safe senders list

To ensure you receive email notifications from Texila American University about your application status, program details, payment receipt confirmation etc., please add ['info@tauedu.org'](mailto:info@tauedu.org) to your safe sender's list. Below is the procedure to add ['info@tauedu.org'](mailto:info@tauedu.org) to your safe sender's list across mail clients.

**Outlook :** Under 'Tools' menu bar, select options. Under 'preferences', select 'junk email' and click on 'safe sender' tab. Click 'add' button. Type ['info@tauedu.org'](mailto:info@tauedu.org) and submit.

**MSN Hotmail :** In the options page, click 'mail' on the left hand menu. Then click on 'junk email protection' and click on 'add senders to safe list'. Type ['info@tauedu.org'](mailto:info@tauedu.org) and then click 'add’.

**Yahoo! Mail :** Under 'addresses' on the top menu, click 'add contact'. Type ['info@tauedu.org'](mailto:info@tauedu.org) in the email field and click 'save'. 

**Gmail :** Go to 'Mail settings' and select 'filters'. 'Create a new filter' and type ['info@tauedu.org'](mailto:info@tauedu.org) at the 'From' field. Click on 'next step' and check 'never send it to spam'. Click on 'create filter'.

#### Privacy Policy Changes

The TAU Team may upgrade this Privacy Policy or modify it every now and then. You should contact us as described below or come back at this Site regularly to acquire a present duplicate of this Privacy Policy. Your ongoing supply of Personal Information comprises your approval of such changes. If we plan to use Details that individually recognizes you different from what we was gathered at enough time, we will make an effort to inform you at least 1 month in advance. You will be given an option as to whether or not formerly offered Details may be used in a new way.

#### How to Access Your Information and Contact Us

If you wish to upgrade any of your personal details or have any concerns about our privacy policies, please get in touch by email at ['info@tauedu.org'](mailto:info@tauedu.org)
